If you're wondering what kind of tools
and prompts people are using to create
these ultra realistic kind of hidden
observer point of view videos using AI,
especially in the biblical niche, look
no further. I'm going to show you how to
do that here today. I'm going to show
you the exact prompts and what tools I
use to generate it. Right here is just
an example of the dozens and dozens that
are going viral this week. Right now,
this one has 3.3 million views and it
was just uploaded yesterday. Okay. So,
here I'm going to play this one for you
and then I'm going to show you one that
I created myself just to test out the
skill, which is a prompt that's packaged
for you, ready to go. I'm going to give
it to you for free. So, let's take a
look at this together.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Now, here on the side, I'm going to show
you the raw output that I was able to
generate myself with the prompt that I
built. And this, there's no editing.
This was the raw output that came out.
All the music, all the sounds, all the
cuts, everything that you see was
generated from a text prompt. So, let's
go ahead and take a look at this.
Now, let's jump into Chad GPT so I can
show you how to get started.
Here I am in a brand new Chad PT
session. And just so you know, you're
going to need at least a $20 a month
plan so you can have the Astra 6.0
model, which is the latest model also,
so you can have access to the plugins.
And then of course, you're also going to
need a membership on Hicksfield. I'm
going to leave all the links down below.
Now, for you to connect your Chad GPT
account to your Hickfield account, it's
pretty simple. You see here on the
bottom where you see plugins. Once you
click plugins, you're going to connect
plugins. And here you're going to browse
and you're going to search for the
Hicksfield plugin. Once you have that
selected, it's going to ask you to
authenticate your account. You log in
once and now it's connected. That means
you can generate videos, images, and
even edits inside of one chat GPT
session. And right here, we're going to
be using the GPT6 Astro model, which is
their latest model. You might notice up
here it says work and then here it says
chat. Now, if you go to chat, it doesn't
give you the ability to see which model
it's using. And I even asked it what
kind of what's the GPT model that you're
using. Is it 5.6? Is it 6.0? No, it says
it's not able to tell. So, the only way
I found to be sure that you're using the
latest model is by going to the work tab
here. And again, you need a paid
membership to do this. I have the $20 a
month plan. So, once I connected my
Hicksfield, now it's time for my skill.
Now, this skill specifically is for a
Bible story setting. So, it's going to
look through the lens of a biblical
story. So, if you say, "Make me a story
about David and Goliath." is going to
create a whole prompt for you in that
style that we just watched.
And now to install the skill, it's
pretty simple. I'm going to leave the
link to the skill below. It's a skill
file, which is essentially just a text
file. Once you have that file, you're
going to upload it to your skills tab.
If you don't know what the skills tabs
are, if you go here on the left side on
Chad GPT, let me go back to the session
here on the left. Open sidebar. Now, you
see here where it says plugins, click on
plugins. And then up here, just like we
switched from chat to work mode, you're
going to see a skills tab. Go ahead and
click on that. And you can see here that
my skills already installed Bible
witness reel. And for you to install it,
simple. Click the plus button here.
Upload from your computer. And then drop
the file in there. And that's going to
be installed right over here.
This is how you call that skill. Once
it's installed, you can simply say
something like this. Use the Bible
hidden witness skill or you don't have
to say skill. It's just the name of it.
It's just the Bible hidden witness to
give me a prompt of Daniel in the lion's
den. Right now, it says here's a Bible
hidden witness version built around the
feeling that the viewer is secretly
present inside the den observing Daniel
from concealment. Notice I didn't say
anything about the hidden witness. It
simply read from the prompt and now it
understands the angle of this prompt. So
now it created the whole prompt for me
here. I'm not going to read through the
whole thing. Now all you have to do is
one of two things. If you have the
Higfield membership plugin already
installed, all you have to do here in
the in the session is say, "Now go ahead
and render this video using Higsfield
Cense 2.5 model." And then you just tell
what aspect ratio you want because
you're going to need to either say 6:9
if you wanted to have a landscape video
for YouTube or 916 if you wanted to make
a real portrait version of this prompt.
And if you don't have Hicksfield, you
can just copy this, take it to your AI
video generation platform and there you
can create your video there. You don't
have to have a reference image. This is
completely from a text to video prompt.
Since I already have my Hickfield
account connected inside of Chat GBT,
I'm simply going to say this. Use this
prompt to connect to the Hicksfield
plugin to generate a Cense 2.5
720p video and the ratio should be 916.
You can go ahead and make a 1080p
version. But I figure that the 720p as a
test is a great way to start it. And
then if you like the way that prompt
comes out, you can go ahead and do the
full HD using the 1080p version. But for
me, for 720, it's perfect if posted
Instagram reels. So once you have that
in there, you're going to go ahead and
send it and it's going to do its thing.
It's going to start connecting to
Hicksfield.
All right. So the generation took about
five minutes. I was able to download it
off a Chad GPT and I added it to this
canvas where we have our kind of our
sandbox where I'm showing you all the
videos. This is the first try. So I
didn't run anything else. I watched it
once and here we're going to watch it
again together.
>> Daniel.
All right. So the ending was a bit long.
So you can definitely trim it at towards
the end there where he kind of comes up
because you wanted to keep it engaging,
right? So you can generate a bunch of
these scenes and then put it all
together just like the one that we
watched over here. If you want this
skill, I'm going to leave a link down in
the description. If you want to try
Hicksfield out, it helps out the channel
at no cost to you. I'm going to leave a
link down below so you can sign up for
Hicksfield. If you want to see more of
the videos I create with biblical
storytelling, that's my niche on
Instagram. I use the same username
there. So if you find me here on
YouTube, you probably can find me on
Instagram. Don't forget to like and
subscribe if you made it all the way to
the end. 90% of the people watching my
videos are not subscribed. So, I would
appreciate it if you give me a boost to
the algorithm by commenting, liking, and
subscribing to the channel. Thanks for
watching and I'll see you next time.
[music]
>> [music]